The fight for tomorrow begins today.
The Tomorrow War is a action, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Chris McKay.
The world is stunned when a group of time travelers arrive from the year 2051 to deliver an urgent message:
Thirty years in the future, mankind is losing a global war against a deadly alien species.
The only hope for survival is for soldiers and civilians from the
present to be transported to the future and join the fight.
Among those recruited is high school teacher and family man Dan Forester.
Determined to save the world for his young daughter, Dan teams up with a brilliant scientist
and his estranged father in a desperate quest to rewrite the fate of the planet.
Dan Forester, played by Chris Pratt.
Colonel Muri Forester, played by Yvonne Strahovski.
James Forester, played by J.K. Simmons.
Emmy Forester, played by Betty Gilpin.
Charlie, played by Sam Richardson.
Dorian, played by Edwin Hodge.
The Tomorrow War is a 2021 American military science-fiction action film directed
by Chris McKay, written by Zach Dean, and starring Chris Pratt.
It was produced by David Ellison, Dana Goldberg, Don Granger, David S.
Goyer, Jules Daly, and Adam Kolbrenner, with a
supporting cast featuring Yvonne Strahovski, J.
Simmons, Betty Gilpin, Sam Richardson, Edwin Hodge, Jasmine
Mathews, Ryan Kiera Armstrong, and Keith Powers.
It follows a mix of present-day soldiers and civilians sent into the
future to fight and stop a devastating alien swarm.
Originally set for theatrical release by Paramount Pictures, the film's distribution rights were acquired by
Amazon Studios due to the COVID-19 pandemic, and digitally released on July 2, 2021, via Prime Video.
With a budget of US$200 million, the film was one of the most
expensive films to debut on a streaming platform.
The Tomorrow War received mixed reviews from critics, with praise for the concept, action sequences, and
performances (particularly Pratt and Richardson), but criticism for its derivative execution.
A sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of world cup, time
travel, global warming, glacier, alien.
The tone is thought_provoking.